Guide to the Recordsings of Sunrise Semester Programs RG.7.3.1.1
New York University Archives
- "AL Labor", February - June, 1982
  - Episode #13 -- Air Copy, May 3, 1982 (Box 93, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0071)
  - Episode #13 -- Standby Copy, May 3, 1982 (Box 94, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0088)
  - Episode #14 -- Air Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 363, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0386)
  - Episode #14 -- Standby Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 140, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0063)
  - Episode #15 -- Air Copy, May 10, 1982 (Box 74, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0037)
  - Episode #15 -- Standby Copy, May 10, 1982 (Box 92, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0075)
  - Episode #16, May 10, 1982 (Box 65, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0129)
  - Episode #17 -- Standby Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 101, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0124)
  - Episode #17 -- Air Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 209, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0581)
  - Episode #18 -- Standby Copy, May 10, 1982 (Box 192, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0541)
  - Episode #18 -- Air Copy, May 10, 1982 (Box 64, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0079)
  - Episode #19 -- Air Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 77, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0040)
  - Episode #19 -- Standby Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 80, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0057)
  - Episode #20 -- Air Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 230, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0035)
  - Episode #20 -- Standby Copy, April 20, 1982 (Box 229, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0097)
  - Episode #21 -- Air Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 208, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0117)
  - Episode #21 -- Standby Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 206, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0500)
  - Episode #22 -- VT1 "A" Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 179, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0566)
  - Episode #22 -- Standby Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 170, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0083)
  - Episode #23 -- "A" Copy, March 30, 1982 (Box 250, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0559)
  - Episode #23 -- "B" Copy, March 30, 1982 (Box 251, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0529)
  - Episode #24 -- Air Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 104, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0425)
  - Episode #24 -- Standby Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 223, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0555)
  - Episode #25 -- Air Copy, March 30, 1982 (Box 90, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0499)
  - Episode #25 -- Standby Copy, March 30, 1982 (Box 248, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0497)
  - Episode #26 -- Air Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 207, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0131)
  - Episode #26 -- Standby Copy, May 4, 1982 (Box 98, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0049)
  - Episode #27 -- Air Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 177, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0047)
  - Episode #27 -- Standby Copy, June 22, 1982 (Box 166, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0567)
  - "B" Copy, April 13, 1982 (Box 204, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0045)
- "Child", April - June, 1982
  - Episode #1 -- Air Copy, April 1, 1982 (Box 91, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0543)
  - Episode #2 -- Air Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 182, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0031)
  - Episode #2 -- Standby Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 130, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0095)
  - Episode #3 -- Air Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 122, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0538)
  - Episode #3 -- Standby Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 219, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0558)
  - Episode #4 -- Air Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 113, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0148)
  - Episode #4 -- Standby Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 259, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0041)
  - Episode #5 -- Air Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 111, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0119)
  - Episode #5 -- Standby Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 70, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0130)
  - Episode #6 -- Air Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 71, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0126)
  - Episode #6 -- Standby Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 202, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0052)
  - Episode #7 -- Air Copy, April 29, 1982 (Box 119, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0536)
  - Episode #7 -- Standby Copy, April 29, 1982 (Box 73, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0537)
  - Episode #8 -- Air Copy, April 29, 1982 (Box 261, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0535)
  - Episode #8 -- NFA "B" Copy, April 29, 1982 (Box 72, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0531)
  - Episode #9 -- Standby Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 183, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0116)
  - Episode #9 -- Air Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 184, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0563)
  - Episode #10 -- Air Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 200, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0042)
  - Episode #10 -- "B" Copy, April 22, 1982 (Box 201, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0125)
  - Episode #11 -- Air Copy, May 17, 1982 (Box 105, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0070)
  - Episode #12 -- Air Copy, April 8, 1982 (Box 109, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0112)
  - Episode #12 -- Standby Copy, April 18, 1982 (Box 175, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0146)
  - Episode #13 -- Air Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 231, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0084)
  - Episode #13 -- Standby Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 260, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0076)
  - Episode #15, April 1, 1982 (Box 197, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0492)
  - Episode #15 -- Air Copy, April 1, 1982 (Box 199, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0554)
  - Episode #16 -- Air Copy, May 11, 1982 (Box 117, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0561)
  - Episode #16 -- Standby Copy, June 17, 1982 (Box 220, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0590)
  - Episode #17 -- Air Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 257, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0494)
  - Episode #17 -- Standby Copy, April 15, 1982 (Box 258, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0439)
  - Episode #18 -- Air Copy, April 8, 1982 (Box 137, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0074)
  - Episode #18 -- Standby Copy, April 8, 1982 (Box 232, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0139)
  - Episode #19 -- Air Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 151, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0589)
  - Episode #19 -- Standby Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 156, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0082)
  - Episode #20 -- Standby Copy, May 17, 1982 (Box 116, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0435)
  - Episode #21 -- Air Copy, May 18, 1982 (Box 241, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0033)
  - Episode #21 -- Standby Copy, May 18, 1982 (Box 242, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0142)
  - Episode #22 -- Air Copy, April 8, 1982 (Box 174, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0072)
  - Episode #22 -- Standby Copy, April 8, 1982 (Box 139, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0564)
  - Episode #23 -- Air Copy, May 18, 1982 (Box 162, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0068)
  - Episode #23 -- Standby Copy, May 18, 1982 (Box 234, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0424)
  - Episode #24 -- Air Copy, May 18, 1982 (Box 235, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0591)
  - Episode #25 -- Air Copy, April 1, 1982 (Box 196, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0582)
  - Episode #26 -- Air Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 147, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0528)
  - Episode #26 -- Standby Copy, May 24, 1982 (Box 245, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0136)
  - Episode #27 -- Standby Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 216, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0440)
  - Episode #27 -- Air Copy, June 15, 1982 (Box 84, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0077)
- "EJ Seniors", April - June, 1982
  - Episode #1 -- Standby Copy, April 16, 1982 (Box 112, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0043)
  - Episode #2 -- Air Copy, April 16, 1982 (Box 187, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0039)
  - Episode #2 -- Air Copy, April 30, 1982 (Box 62, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0062)
  - Episode #2 -- Standby Copy, April 16, 1982 (Box 228, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0423)
  - Episode #3 -- Air Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 256, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0138)
  - Episode #3 -- Standby Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 254, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0147)
  - Episode #4 -- "A" Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 253, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0065)
  - Episode #4 -- "B" Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 69, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0502)
  - Episode #5 -- Air Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 180, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0585)
  - Episode #5 -- Standby Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 66, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0504)
  - Episode #6 -- Air Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 108, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0055)
  - Episode #6 -- Standby Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 217, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0086)
  - Episode #7 -- Air Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 255, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0078)
  - Episode #7 -- "B" Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 252, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0090)
  - Episode #8 -- Air Copy, April 30, 1982 (Box 210, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0580)
  - Episode #8 -- Standby Copy, April 30, 1982 (Box 195, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0493)
  - Episode #9 -- Standby Copy, May 25, 1982 (Box 155, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0557)
  - Episode #10 -- Air Copy, June 1, 1982 (Box 150, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0556)
  - Episode #10 -- Standby Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 167, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0569)
  - Episode #11 -- Air Copy, June 1, 1982 (Box 157, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0442)
  - Episode #11 -- Standby Copy, June 1, 1982 (Box 158, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0578)
  - Episode #12 -- Air Copy, June 1, 1982 (Box 225, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0038)
  - Episode #13 -- Air Copy, undated (Box 246, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0058)
  - Episode #13 -- Standby Copy, June 1, 1982 (Box 161, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0586)
  - Episode #13 -- Standby Copy, undated (Box 154, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0113)
  - Episode #14 -- Air Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 141, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0089)
  - Episode #14 -- Standby Copy, May 12, 1982 (Box 181, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0421)
  - Episode #15 -- Air Copy, June 7, 1982 (Box 244, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0157)
  - Episode #15 -- Standby Copy, June 7, 1982 (Box 142, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0110)
  - Episode #16 -- "A" Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 133, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0153)
  - Episode #16 -- Standby Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 171, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0579)
  - Episode #17 -- Air Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 134, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0154)
  - Episode #17 -- Standby Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 226, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0533)
  - Episode #18 -- "A" Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 233, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0151)
  - Episode #18 -- Air Copy, June 14, 1982 (Box 212, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0137)
  - Episode #19 -- Air Copy, June 21, 1982 (Box 123, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0438)
  - Episode #19 -- Standby Copy, June 21, 1982 (Box 125, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0437)
  - Episode #20 -- Air Copy, May 25, 1982 (Box 148, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0128)
  - Episode #20 -- Standby Copy, May 25, 1982 (Box 132, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0044)
  - Episode #21 -- Air Copy, June 7, 1982 (Box 146, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0069)
  - Episode #21 -- Standby Copy, undated (Box 236, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0103)
  - Episode #22 -- Standby Copy, June 7, 1982 (Box 218, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0588)
  - Episode #23 -- Air Copy, June 28, 1982 (Box 185, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0587)
  - Episode #23 -- Standby Copy, June 28, 1982 (Box 240, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0532)
  - Episode #24 -- Air Copy, June 28, 1982 (Box 238, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0064)
  - Episode #25 -- Air Copy, April 30, 1982 (Box 97, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0434)
  - Episode #25 -- Standby Copy, April 30, 1982 (Box 99, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0091)
  - Episode #26 -- "A" Copy, June 21, 1982 (Box 124, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0135)
  - Episode #26 -- Standby Copy, June 21, 1982 (Box 85, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0073)
  - Episode #27 -- Air Copy, June 21, 1982 (Box 178, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0565)
  - Episode #28 -- Standby Copy, June 24, 1982 (Box 126, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0542)
- "TH Ethics", April - June, 1982
  - Episode #1 -- Air Copy, April 28, 1982 (Box 63, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0132)
  - Episode #1, April 28, 1982 (Box 68, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0107)
  - Episode #2 -- Air Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 136, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0099)
  - Episode #2 -- Standby Copy, May 19, 1982 (Box 129, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0054)
  - Episode #3 -- Standby Copy, April 28, 1982 (Box 67, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0092)
  - Episode #3 -- Standby Copy, April 28, 1982 (Box 193, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0030)
  - Episode #4 -- Air Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 205, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0109)
  - Episode #4 -- Standby Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 81, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0544)
  - Episode #5 -- Air Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 78, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0436)
  - Episode #5 -- Standby Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 100, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0501)
  - Episode #6 -- Air Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 194, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0158)
  - Episode #6 -- Standby Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 191, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0133)
  - Episode #7 -- Air Copy, May 19, 1982 (Box 131, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0560)
  - Episode #7 -- Standby Copy, May 5, 1982 (Box 135, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0098)
  - Episode #8 -- Air Copy, 1982 (Box 149, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0094)
  - Episode #8 -- Standby Copy, May 26, 1982 (Box 159, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0583)
  - Episode #9 -- Standby Copy, 26 May 1982 (Box 221, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0034)
  - Episode #10 -- Air Copy, May 19, 1982 (Box 143, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0118)
  - Episode #10 -- Standby Copy, May 19, 1982 (Box 128, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0141)
  - Episode #11 -- Standby Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 164, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0056)
  - Episode #11 -- Air Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 227, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0121)
  - Episode #12 -- Air Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 118, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0443)
  - Episode #12 -- Standby Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 152, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0140)
  - Episode #13 -- Air Copy, May 26, 1982 (Box 160, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0562)
  - Episode #13 -- Standby Copy, May 26, 1982 (Box 243, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0495)
  - Episode #14 -- Air Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 145, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0066)
  - Episode #14 -- Standby Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 120, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0123)
  - Episode #15 -- Air Copy, April 26, 1982 (Box 190, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0061)
  - Episode #16 -- Air Copy, June 9, 1982 (Box 82, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0122)
  - Episode #16 -- Standby Copy, June 9, 1982 (Box 114, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0036)
  - Episode #17 -- Air Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 222, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0498)
  - Episode #18 -- Air Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 237, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0422)
  - Episode #18 -- Standby Copy, June 30, 1982 (Box 169, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0115)
  - Episode #19 -- Air Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 168, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0108)
  - Episode #19 -- Standby Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 86, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0093)
  - Episode #20 -- "B" Copy, June 9, 1982 (Box 163, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0067)
  - Episode #21 -- Air Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 115, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0503)
  - Episode #21 -- Standby Copy, June 2, 1982 (Box 153, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0106)
  - Episode #22 -- Air Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 107, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0114)
  - Episode #22 -- Standby Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 215, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0530)
  - Episode #23 -- Air Copy, April 23, 1982 (Box 211, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0539)
  - Episode #23 -- Air Copy, June 23, 1982 (Box 214, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0104)
  - Episode #24 -- Air Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 83, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0145)
  - Episode #24 -- Standby Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 239, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0568)
  - Episode #25 -- Air Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 106, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0059)
  - Episode #25 -- Standby Copy, June 16, 1982 (Box 144, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0584)
  - Episode #26 -- Air Copy, June 23, 1982 (Box 224, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0032)
  - Episode #27 -- Air Copy, June 23, 1982 (Box 165, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0155)
  - Episode #27 -- Standby Copy, undated (Box 127, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0096)
  - Episode #28 -- Air Copy, June 9, 1982 (Box 121, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0156)
- Medgar Evars / Adelphi, March - June, 1982
  - "Open and Close Reel" -- Bergen, RAMAP, Medgar Evers, March 30, 1982 (Box 176, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0152)
  - "Open / Close", April 5, 1982 (Box 198, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0149)
  - "Adelphi Remote Insert", June 14, 1982 (Box 213, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0080)
- "English H6 / Sociology S1" with David Greene and Joseph Bram, undated
  - February 3-5 -- "Moby Dick," "Sociology Defined," "Scientific Sociology"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0366)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1978p1, 1978p2)
  - February 10-17 -- "Symbolism in Moby Dick," "Concept of culture, "Interpreting Moby Dick," "Culture and the Individual," "Madame Bovary," "Language"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0365)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1979p1, 1979p2)
  - February 19-21 -- "Madame Bovary, "Mores and Folkways," "Crime and Punishment," "Social Control"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0364)
    - Access CD (Box 15, Cd 1980p1)
  - February 24-26 -- "Crime and Punishment," "Role-Playing," "Age-Specific Behavior"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0376)
    - Access CD (Box 15, Cd 1981p1)
  - February 28 - April 3 -- "Crime and Punishment," "Behavior Roles," "Conflict in Social Life"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0375)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1982p1, 1982p2)
  - March 5-7 -- "A Doll's House," "The Nature of Hostility," "The Wild Duck," "Competition vs. Cooperation"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0374)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1983p1, 1983p2)
  - March 10-12 -- "Thomas Hardy," "Society Molds Human Potential," "Jude the Obscure," "Society Shapes the Child"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0373)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1984p1, 1984p2)
  - April 18 -- "The English Lyric, Wordsworth, Intimations," "Marriage and the Family / Selection of Mates," "Ode to the West Wind," "Forms of Family Structure"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0372)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1985p1, 1985p2)
  - April 25-28 -- "Keats' Ode to a Grecian Urn," "The Changing Family in the Modern World," "Tennyson's Ulysses," "Science and Technology"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0371)
    - Access CD (Box 15, Cd 1986p1)
  - April 30 -- "Browning's My Last Duchess," "Science and Technology"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0370)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1987p1, 1987p2)
  - May 5-9 -- "Hopkin's The Windhover," "Religion and Society," "Yeats' The Wild Swans at Coole," "Demography," "Yeats' In Memory of Maj," "Robert Gregory," "Cultural Change and the Diffusion of Ideas"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0369)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1988p1, 1988p2)
  - May 12-14 -- "Yeats Sailing to Byzantium," "Trends in Social Change," "Yeats Among School Children," "Sociology in the Modern World"
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0368)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1989p1, 1989p2)
  - Unlabeled session
    According to repository notes, this recording's content may be either English H6 / Sociology S1 or Russian Literature.
    - Original recording (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 7.3.1.1.0367)
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 1990p1, 1990p2)
- "Social Philosophers of the Western World" with Professor Henry Magid, undated
  - "From Myth to Reason"
    - Original recording
    - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd 5:9, 5:10)
- Unlabeled video, undated (Box 16, 1 inch video reel 7.3.1.1.0143)